Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - E
        - E-A-Ski - Blast if I have to; Friday night, 1995; SR-13906; E-A-Ski; Scarface (Box 253)
          Catalog # SPRO 50875; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50875-A RE-1
          Priority Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - E-A-Ski - Blast if I have to; Friday night, 1995; SR-13907; E-A-Ski; Scarface (Box 253)
        - E-A-Ski - Blast if I have to; Friday night, 1995; SR-13908; E-A-Ski; Scarface (Box 253)
        - E-A-Ski - Blast if I have to; Friday night, 1995; SR-13909; E-A-Ski; Scarface (Box 253)
        - E-Klektik - Matacana madness, 1994; SR-13910; E-Klektik (Box 253)
          Catalog # WALLT 001; A-side Matrix # WALL 01 A1
          Wall of Sound
          United Kingdom
        - ET - Candy, 1986; SR-13911; ET (Box 253)
          Catalog # TED1-2635; A-side Matrix # TED1-2635-AS-1S
          Total Experience Records
        - ET - Magic in the air (all around you everywhere), 1985; SR-13912; ET (Box 253)
          Catalog # TED1-2638; A-side Matrix # TED1-2638-AS-2
        - Eagles - The long run, 1979; SR-13913; Eagles (Box 253)
          Catalog # 5E-508; A-side Matrix # 5E 508 A
          Asylum Records
        - Earland, Charles - The Dynamite Brothers (original motion picture soundtrack ), 1974; SR-13914; Earland, Charles (Box 253)
          Catalog # P-10082; A-side Matrix # P10082A
          Prestige
          Berkeley, California
        - Early, James - Rock on me, 1988; SR-13915; Early, James (Box 253)
          Catalog # D-296; A-side Matrix # D-296 A
          Volt
        - Earth messengers - Ivory towers, 1989; SR-13917; Earth messengers (Box 253)
          Catalog # MLPS 9839; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9839-A
          Mango
          New York, New York
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Remixes, 2002; SR-13918; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # SIJP 3; A-side Matrix # SIJP-3-A
          Soul Source
          Japan
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1971; SR-13919; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # WS 1905; A-side Matrix # SCO1 1905-A
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Powerlight, 1983; SR-13920; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # TC 38367; A-side Matrix # PAL 38367-3H
          Columbia
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Heritage, 1990; SR-13921; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # C 45268; A-side Matrix # PAL-45268 1A
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - System of survival (12" mixes), 1987; SR-13922; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 44 07475; A-side Matrix # XSS-176355-1A
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Let me talk, 1980; SR-13923; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # AS 853; A-side Matrix # XSS-167522-1C
          ARC
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Spend the night, 1993; SR-13924; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6574; A-side Matrix # PROA16574SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Side by side, 1983; SR-13925; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # AS 1648; A-side Matrix # XSS 169285
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Boogie wonderland, 1979; SR-13926; Earth, Wind & Fire; Emotions (Box 253)
          Catalog # 23-10950; A-side Matrix # XSS-165779-1C
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Sunday morning, 1993; SR-13928; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6286; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 6286 SR1
          United States
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - The need of love, 1971; SR-13929; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # WS 1958; A-side Matrix # WS-1-1958 LW-1
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - The best of Earth, Wind & Fire vol. I, 1978; SR-13930; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # FC 35647; A-side Matrix # PAL-35647-1AE
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Magnetic, 1983; SR-13931; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 44-04211; A-side Matrix # XSS 169496-1F
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Electric universe, 1983; SR-13932; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # QC 38980; A-side Matrix # PAL 38980-1F
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Fall in love with me, 1982; SR-13933; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # AS 1617; A-side Matrix # XSS 169231-1B
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Let's groove (special radio re-mix), 1981; SR-13934; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # AS 1342; A-side Matrix # XSS 168364 1A
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Turn on (the beat box), 1988; SR-13935; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 44 08140; A-side Matrix # XSS-08140-A
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Saturday nite, 1976; SR-13936; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 23-10512; A-side Matrix # XSS 163201 2B
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Heritage, 1990; SR-13937; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 44 73157; A-side Matrix # XSS-73157A 1A G1
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Got to get you into my life, 1978; SR-13938; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # 23-10786; A-side Matrix # XSS-164387-1D
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - 4 track EP, SR-13939; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 253)
          Catalog # TPFS-001; A-side Matrix # TPFS-001 A
          The Power of Funk & Soul
        - Earthquakes Debax - One to go, 1995; SR-13940; Earthquakes Debax (Box 253)
          No entry in Discogs.
          Catalog # SI 0054; A-side Matrix # SI-0054-A
          Spice Island Records
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Various - Earplay Entertainment Ep, 1996; SR-13941; Twist, Oliver; Khénya (Box 253)
          Catalog # EE001; A-side Matrix # EE-001-A
          Earplay Entertainment
        - Incredible Ease - Who rocks?, 1998; SR-13942; Incredible Ease (Box 253)
          Catalog # EQR32001; A-side Matrix # EQR-32001-A
          E.Q. Recordings
          Canada
        - Ease Drop - Doorway, 1999; SR-13943; Ease Drop (Box 253)
          Catalog # KR1015B; A-side Matrix # KR-1015-A
          Kram Records and Productions
          Orlando, Florida
        - Easton, Sheena - Telefone (long distance love affair), 1983; SR-13944; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # EMI 7814; A-side Matrix # 7814-1-P-2
          EMI America
          Hollywood, California
        - East Side Hustlas - Pourin' Moe; Project vet; Places, diamonds & oasis, 1996; SR-13946; East Side Hustlas (Box 253)
          Catalog # MSR112296; A-side Matrix # MSR-112296-A
          Mad Street Records
        - Eastbound Expressway - Never let go, 1978; SR-13947; Eastbound Expressway (Box 253)
          Catalog # AVI 12-238 D; A-side Matrix # 078-12-238-A
          AVI Records
        - Eastbound Expressway - Never let go; Cloudburst, 1978; SR-13948; Eastbound Expressway (Box 253)
          Catalog # AVDJ 12-238 D; A-side Matrix # 078-12-238-A
        - Easton, Sheena - Sugar hill, 1984; SR-13949; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13950. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-9312; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9312-21
        - Easton, Sheena - Sugar hill (dance mix), 1985; SR-13950; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13949. Different discs.
          Catalog # V-7852; A-side Matrix # V-1-7852-21
        - Easton, Sheena - Strut, 1984; SR-13951; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # SPRO-9230; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9230-21
        - Easton, Sheena - Eternity (Shep Pettibone mix), 1987; SR-13952; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # 12EM 9; A-side Matrix # 12 EM 9 A-2-1-1
          EMI
        - Easton, Sheena - What comes naturally, 1991; SR-13953; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # L33-1347; A-side Matrix # MCA 10642-BG2
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Easton, Sheena - Sweat, 1984; SR-13954; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # V-7847-1; A-side Matrix # V-1-7847-Z2
        - Easton, Sheena - Days like this, 1989; SR-13955; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # L33-17771; A-side Matrix # MCA-8657-FDS-2
        - Easton, Sheena - Jimmy Mack, 1986; SR-13956; Easton, Sheena (Box 253)
          Catalog # SPRO-9588; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9588-Z1
        - Eastsidaz - Duces 'n trayz - the old fashioned way (Disc one), 2001; SR-13957; Eastsidaz; Snoop Dogg (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13958. Double album.
          Catalog # TVT 2230-1; A-side Matrix # TV-2230-1-A
          TVT Records
        - Eastsidaz - Duces 'n trayz - the old fashioned way (Disc two), 2001; SR-13958; Eastsidaz; Snoop Dogg (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13957. Double album.
          Catalog # TVT 2230-1; A-side Matrix # TV-2230-1-C
        - Ruff Ryders - Eastside Ryders, 2001; SR-13960; Ruff Ryders; Styles, Holiday; Eastsidaz (Box 254)
          Catalog # INTR-10650-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10650-1-A
          Interscope Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Clint Eastwood & General Saint - Two bad D.J., 2012; SR-13961; Clint Eastwood & General Saint (Box 254)
          Catalog # GREL 24; A-side Matrix # GREL 24 A
          Greensleeves Records
          London, United Kingdom
        - Clint Eastwood & General Saint - Matty Gunga Walk, 1982; SR-13962; Clint Eastwood & General Saint (Box 254)
          Damaged
          Catalog # GRED 100; A-side Matrix # GRED 100 A
        - Clint Eastwood & General Saint - Shame & scandal in the family, 1982; SR-13963; Clint Eastwood & General Saint (Box 254)
          Catalog # 12 OINK 3; A-side Matrix # 12 OINK BA
        - Easy Earl - The boulevard brut; Easiest the Earl, 1988; SR-13964; Easy Earl; DJ Fantasy B; Street Rapper Godzilla (Box 254)
          Catalog # RR-001; A-side Matrix # RR-001-A
          Ray Ray Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - Easy Moe Bee - Good life, 1999; SR-13965; Easy Moe Bee (Box 254)
          Catalog # SPRO 81156; A-side Matrix # SPRO 81156-A
        - Eazy-E - BNK; 24 hrs to live (remix), 1998; SR-13967; Eazy-E; MC Ren (Box 254)
          Catalog # EAS 41302; A-side Matrix # XSS-41302-A-1A
          Ruthless Records
        - Eazy-E - Creep 'n crawl, 1996; SR-13968; Eazy-E (Box 254)
          Catalog # 88561-6336-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6336-1 A1
        - Eazy-E - Just tah let u know, 1995; SR-13969; Eazy-E (Box 254)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0424; A-side Matrix # 88561-5532-1A
        - Eazy-E - Black ni**a killa, 1998; SR-13970; Eazy-E (Box 254)
          Catalog # EAS 6503; A-side Matrix # RR-6503-1 A
        - Eazy-E - Eazy-duz-it, 1988; SR-13971; Eazy-E (Box 254)
          Catalog # SL57100; A-side Matrix # SL-STREET-57100-Z2
        - Ēbn/Ōzn - AEIOU sometimes Y, 1983; SR-13972; Ēbn/Ōzn (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13973. Different discs.
          Catalog # EAOR 4910; A-side Matrix # STEDO 67915-A-6
          Elektra
        - Ēbn/Ōzn - AEIOU sometimes Y, 1983; SR-13973; Ēbn/Ōzn (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13972. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-67915; A-side Matrix # STEDO 67915-A-6
        - Ēbn/Ōzn - AEIOU sometimes Y, 1983; SR-13974; Ēbn/Ōzn (Box 254)
        - Eboman - Bounce to diss E.P., 1997; SR-13975; Eboman (Box 254)
          Catalog # XLEP 124; A-side Matrix # XLEP 124A
          XL Recordings
        - Ebony Vibe Everlasting - Groove of love, 1994; SR-13978; Ebony Vibe Everlasting (Box 254)
          Catalog # GAS12 54930; A-side Matrix # GAS 12152 PDS-2
          Gasoline Alley Records
        - Echo & The Bunnymen - Echo & The Bunnymen, 1987; SR-13979; Echo & The Bunnymen (Box 254)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # WX 108; A-side Matrix # 242137-1-A
          WEA
        - E.C.P. - Straight lace playaz, 1995; SR-13980; E.C.P. (Box 254)
          Catalog # 12-PO 335; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-335 A
          Wrap Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Ectasy, Passion, & Pain - The Dance Masters, SR-13719; Ectasy, Passion, & Pain; Barbara Roy; Bobby Caldwell (Box 254)
          Catalog # DM-1263; A-side Matrix # DTC-014-A
          Dance Masters
        - Ed O.G. & Da Bulldogs - Love comes and goes, 1994; SR-13981; Ed O.G. & Da Bulldogs; Ed O.G. (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13982. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 858 337-1; A-side Matrix # 858-337-1-A
          Chemistry Records
        - Ed O.G. & Da Bulldogs - Love comes and goes, 1994; SR-13982; Ed O.G. & Da Bulldogs; Ed O.G. (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13981. Multiple copies.
        - Ed O.G. - Shed a tear, 2005; SR-13983; Ed O.G.; EDO G; Rock, Pete (Box 254)
          Catalog # FB-2520; A-side Matrix # FB-2520-A-RE
          Fat Beats
          Canoga Park, California
        - Eddie "D" - Adlib, 1981; SR-13984; Eddie "D" (Box 254)
          Catalog # ALI-121080; A-side Matrix # ALI-12180-A-1
          Park Place
        - Eddie "D" - Cold cash $ money, 1984; SR-13985; Eddie "D" (Box 254)
          Catalog # PA-1403; A-side Matrix # PA-1403-A
          Pop Art Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Eddie F. - Let's get it on (the album) (Disc one), 1994; SR-13986; Eddie F.; Untouchables (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13987. Double album.
          Catalog # 314530313-1; A-side Matrix # 314530313-RE-1A
          Motown
        - Eddie F. - Let's get it on (the album) (Disc two), 1994; SR-13987; Eddie F.; Untouchables (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13986. Double album.
          Catalog # 314530313-1; A-side Matrix # 314530313-RE-1C
        - Eddie F. - Let's get it on (the album) (Disc one), 1994; SR-13988; Eddie F.; Untouchables (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13989. Double album.
        - Eddie F. - Let's get it on (the album) (Disc two), 1994; SR-13989; Eddie F.; Untouchables (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13988. Double album.
        - Edge - Do ya dirt, 1994; SR-13992; Edge (Box 254)
          Catalog # RR 834; A-side Matrix # RR 834-A
          Represent Records
        - Edwards, Bernard - Your love is good to me, 1983; SR-13993; Edwards, Bernard (Box 254)
          Catalog # DMD 652; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44881-1
          Atlantic
        - Edwards, Dee - Don't sit down, 1979; SR-13994; Edwards, Dee (Box 254)
          Catalog # DSKO 167; A-side Matrix # ST-DK 36907-1
          Cotillion
        - Edwards, Dee - Put your love on the line, 1980; SR-13995; Edwards, Dee (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13996. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # DMD 250; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-39145-1
        - Edwards, Dee - Put your love on the line, 1980; SR-13996; Edwards, Dee (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13995. Multiple copies.
        - Edwards, Dennis - Don't look any further; Is it in; Dance across the floor, 1990; SR-13997; Edwards, Dennis; Horne, Jimmy "Bo" (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13998. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SPEC-1483; A-side Matrix # SPEC-1483A
          Unidisc
        - Edwards, Dennis - Don't look any further; Is it in; Dance across the floor, 1990; SR-13998; Edwards, Dennis; Horne, Jimmy "Bo" (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-13997. Multiple copies.
        - Edwards, Sally - Everbody dancing to Lotay Lah, 1995; SR-13999; Edwards, Sally; Gemini Band (Box 254)
          Catalog # JMC-1094; A-side Matrix # JMC 1094-A
          Jamaican Me Crazy Records
        - Edwards, Winston - At 10 Downing Street - Dub conference, 1980; SR-14000; Edwards, Winston; Blackbeard (Box 254)
          Catalog # LTM 1025; A-side Matrix # LTM1025A
          Celluloid
          France
        - Ee-De - Let's get to it (the krunk love song), 2003; SR-14001; Ee-De (Box 254)
          Catalog # NME003; A-side Matrix # L-13698MF NME-002A
          NME Records
        - Eek-A-Mouse - Skidip!, 1982; SR-14002; Eek-A-Mouse (Box 254)
          Catalog # GREL 41; A-side Matrix # GREL 41 A
        - Ruffnexx Sound System - Eeny meeny (sweet temptation), 1995; SR-14003; Ruffnexx Sound System (Box 254)
          Catalog # 0-43578; A-side Matrix # 0-43578-A-SR1
          Qwest Records
        - East Island - Particular purpose, 1998; SR-14004; East Island (Box 254)
          Catalog # 12GOTEL001; A-side Matrix # 12GOTEL-001 A-1
          Gotcha!
        - Effective Force - Diamond bullet, 1991; SR-14005; Effective Force (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14006. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 0700 003; A-side Matrix # 0700 003-2A
          MFS
          Berlin, Germany
        - Effective Force - Diamond bullet, 1991; SR-14006; Effective Force (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14005. Multiple copies.
        - Egoslavia - Egoslavia, 1982; SR-14007; Egoslavia (Box 254)
          Catalog # DM-82053; A-side Matrix # DHS-14-A
          91/2 x 16" Records
          Washington DC
        - Egyptian Lover - Get into it, 1990; SR-14008; Egyptian Lover (Box 254)
          Catalog # DMSR 00993; A-side Matrix # DMSR-00993-A S-23076
          Egyptian Empire Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Egyptian Lover - The lover (long version), 1986; SR-14009; Egyptian Lover (Box 254)
          Catalog # DMSR-00771; A-side Matrix # DSMR 00771-A
        - Eightball & M.J.G. - Don't flex, 1998; SR-14010; Eightball & M.J.G. (Box 254)
          Catalog # U8P-1447; A-side Matrix # U8P-1447-A
          Universal Records
        - Eightball & M.J.G. - Break 'em off, 1995; SR-14011; Eightball & M.J.G. (Box 254)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0419; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0419A
          Suave House
          Houston, Texas
        - Eightball & M.J.G. - Throw your hands up; Armed robbery, 1999; SR-14012; Eightball & M.J.G. (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14013. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # U8P-1576; A-side Matrix # U8P-1576-A-2
        - Eightball & M.J.G. - Throw your hands up; Armed robbery, 1999; SR-14013; Eightball & M.J.G. (Box 254)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14012. Multiple copies.
        - Eightball & M.J.G. - Players night out, 1994; SR-14014; Eightball & M.J.G. (Box 254)
          Catalog # SR 00002; A-side Matrix # SR-2-A-GIA
          Suave Records
        - Eightball - Pure uncut, 1998; SR-14015; Eightball (Box 254)
          Catalog # U8P-1268; A-side Matrix # U8P-1268 A
        - Eightball - My homeboy's girlfriend, 1998; SR-14016; Eightball (Box 254)
          Catalog # U8P-1338; A-side Matrix # U8P-1338 A1B
        - Eire Apparent - Sunrise, 1969; SR-14017; Eire Apparent (Box 255)
          Catalog # BDS 5031; A-side Matrix # BDS 5031A-3
          Buddah Records
        - Eko - TKO, 1983; SR-14018; Eko (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14019. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # NI 5075; A-side Matrix # N 1-5075 AS-1 B
          NIA Records
        - Eko - TKO, 1983; SR-14019; Eko (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14018. Multiple copies.
        - E.K.O. - Keep it shining, 1998; SR-14020; E.K.O. (Box 255)
          Catalog # MM 88450-1; A-side Matrix # MM 88450-1A
          Moonshine Music
        - El Da Sensei - Crowd pleasa; Natural feel good, 2006; SR-14022; El Da Sensei (Box 255)